good afternoon, look, I’ll ask people from
добрый день на смотрите я у людей из
Russia how you feel about the war
россии спрошу как вы относитесь к войне
in ukraine
в украине
anti-war
антивоенная
interesting
интересно
from personal if there is a solid hidden group
с личных если твердого скрыто группа
there is, well, just loves definitely
есть ну как просто любит определенно
forbidden doctors
запрещенное врачи
say
говорят
cool souls I saw a video in
прикольно души я вчера видел видео в
khabarovsk yesterday two guys went out
хабаровске два парня выходила
there is such a group called it  and water
есть такая группа называется она а вода
info
info
organizing a summary of who where when the
организация сводки о том кто где когда
defender came out so it’s
защитница так это
just
просто
in which cities you have kicks
в каких городах у вас есть кики
anti-war kitanu actions in support of
антивоенные китану акции в поддержку
large actions probably now there’s
крупных акции наверно сейчас нету
just no type going out there one by two
просто типа выходит там по одному по два
people will absorb
человека впитают
Khabarovsk maybe there
хабаровск может быть там
Novosibirsk
новосибирске
such largest Yekaterinburg
такие крупнейшие екатеринбург
where there are a lot of people just
там где много людей на просто
for example, I asked people how,
например вот я у людей спрашивал как
which does not support a war but
который которая не поддерживает войну но
not a hot one, we don’t go out because
не горячую мы не выходим потому что нас
they’ll beat us right there, beat us, shoot us, that’s
сразу там побьют изобьют расстреляет вот
how tough the system reacts there
насколько жесткая система реагирует там
0 these single pickets, well, firstly, it’s
0 эти одиночные пикеты ну во-первых
easy to stand in the center  cities more
простая простоять в центре города больше
than five minutes is absolutely unreal
чем пять минут абсолютно нереально
sweat  why I’ll pick you up right away, and they’ll
потому что сразу тебя заберу причем
take me away, probably
заберут меня вот задерживали наверно
five police officers detained at least one pointer to the
пять полицейских хоть один указатель на
TCG, but in general, for example, in large
ттг а вот в целом например больших
cities like St. Petersburg there, of course, it’s tough
городах типа питера там конечно жестко
there, like torture, there are police there and
там типа пытки есть в полиции там их и
shockers are used by
шокерами фигачит
ordinary small ones, rather
обычных маленьких скорее
Novosibirsk, these are not small
новосибирска это не маленькие
thoughts, but  anyway, like it’s siberia, it
мыслей но все равно типа это сибирь это
’s like even in something
как бы даже в чем-то
else a little bit of the state understood
другое другое немного государства понял
the state the state of moscow is far away
на государство государство москва далеко
we are here ourselves when, for example, let’s tell
мы тут сами когда а например скажем вас
you how people basically support
вот люди как в основном поддерживает
wars don’t support the bulk of the
войны не поддерживают основная масса
question,
вопрос
for example, yesterday we drove along the highway there
например вчера мы ездили по трассе там
saw a lot of cars, I thought how many
видели много машин я думала много ли
cars would be with the letter z, and in fact
будет машин буквой z да и их по факту
there weren’t so many of them, maybe for the
было не так уж и много может быть я за
whole time we were driving there I was confused with and
все время пока мы там ехали путать со и
in this I’ll hit 10 to the maximum, but it’s
в этом стукну на 10 до максимум но это
not so much in  in general, my
не так уж и много в целом молодежь мое
entourage supports the youth, but the older
окружение поддерживает но более старшее
generation is possible, as it were, that is,
поколение возможно как бы то есть
it
это
will drink for it, because I
будет за это пить потому что я очень
meet a lot in roulette like this  people
много в рулетке так встречаю людей
who are there they are sensitive yes we withstand the
которые там они чуткой да мы выдерживаем
war for a year the seams attacked us there
войну году швы на нас напали там
biolaboratories for all this nonsense like
биолаборатории на весь этот бред типа
knowing this and when it’s no longer there to indicate there you
знать это и когда уже нет указать там вы
bombed tmax in rubles for eight years and
за восемь лет бомбили tmax в рублях а
let’s say we bombed the donbass for 8 years well you
допустим мы бомбили донбасс 8 лет ну вы
now bombed the Russians visual
сейчас разбомбили русские зрительный
ferret in mariupol twice well, why
хорька в мариуполе twice ну зачем чего
can’t they 8 date hard but for example here is the
не могут 8 дата тяжело а например вот
youth so here but a few from a lot of
молодежь так вот но несколько от много
youth and who are for the war so
молодежь и которые за войну так